grab-media.com 2012-11-14

# Grab | Privacy Policy

At Grab Media ("Grab Media," "we" or "us"), we know that every user ("You" or "Your") of the Internet is concerned about privacy, so we developed this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect, use, and disclose information about users of our website located at [www.grab-media.com](http://www.grab-media.com/) (the "Site"). As a guiding principal, our mission at Grab Media is to provide our users with access to a wide selection of enjoyable, interesting, and entertaining videos (we call that our "Service"), and we hope your experience on our Site and Service is enjoyable. In order to provide this Service and to optimize the Site, we may collect information about You as described below in this Privacy Policy. Read on and we will tell You how this all works.

By using the Site, You are accepting the policies and practices described in this Privacy Policy. Each time You visit the Site and any time You voluntarily provide us with information, You agree that You are consenting to our collection, use and disclosure of the information that You provide, and You are consenting to receive emails or otherwise be contacted, as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into Grab Media's Terms of Use. If a term is capitalized and not defined in this Privacy Policy, it is defined in Grab Media's Terms of Use. Whether or not you register or create any kind of account with Grab Media, this Privacy Policy applies to all users of the Site.

INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU MAY BE PROCESSED IN THE UNITED STATES OR ELSEWHERE IN THE WORLD. YOU UNDERSTAND THAT LAWS IN THE JURISDICTION WHERE THAT INFORMATION IS PROCESSED MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE LAWS IN OTHER COUNTRIES, INCLUDING THE LAWS WHERE YOU LIVE.

So that we are clear about the terminology we are using, when we use the phrase "Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy, we mean information about You that is personally identifiable to You, like Your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number. When we use the phrase "Non-Personal Information" in this Privacy Policy, we mean information that is not associated with or linked to Your Personal Information. Non-Personal Information does not enable identification of or contact with individual persons.

### Our Information Collection Through Third-Party Sites

In addition to operating the Site, Grab Media is in the business of making videos available to its numerous business partners, who include those videos within their own websites. In connection with delivering videos or advertisements to those websites, we may collect information from the end users of those websites. If we do, our collection, use and disclosure of information will be performed as described in this Privacy Policy, in the same manner as if the information were collected through the Site.

### Children

The Site is not directed to children and children are not eligible to use our Services. Protecting the privacy of children is very important to us. We do not collect or maintain Personal Information from people we actually know are under 18 years of age, and no part of our Site or Service is designed to attract people under 18 years of age. If we later learn that a user is under 18 years of age, we will take steps to remove that user's Personal Information from our databases and to prevent the user from utilizing the Site and the Service.

### How We Collect Information

We do not collect Personal Information from You unless you voluntarily provide it to us.

From time to time we may request optional information to support Your access to the Site or Services. For example, when You sign up to receive information about products or services that may be of interest to You, we may collect Your email address and other information related to your request. When You communicate with us by sending us an email, or otherwise complete online forms, surveys or contest entries, we will collect any information that is contained in Your communications with us. In generally, it is not necessary to provide Us Your Personal Information in order to use most features of the Site, and You can choose not to provide us with any particular Personal Information, but please be aware that this may limit the features of the Site or Services You are able to use.

### Information Collected Via Technology

As You use the Site or Services, certain information may also be passively collected and stored on our or our service providers' server logs, including Your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We may also use Cookies, Web beacons, and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of Your visit and the information You viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on the Site You clicked. This type of information is collected to make the Site or Services and solutions more useful to You and to tailor the experience with the Site or Services to meet Your special interests and needs.

An "Internet protocol address" or "IP Address" is a number that is automatically assigned to Your computer when You use the Internet. In some cases Your IP Address stays the same from browser session to browser session; but if You use a consumer internet access provider, Your IP Address probably varies from session to session. We, or our service providers, may track Your IP Address when You access the Site or Services.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to Your computer's hard drive while You are viewing a website. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once You close Your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on Your computer until You delete them) to provide You with a more personal and interactive experience with the Site or Services. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Your Internet browser help file directions. If You choose to disable Cookies, some areas of the Site or Services may not work properly.

"Web Beacons" (sometimes also known as "Web bugs" or clear GIFs) take two forms. The first form of Web Beacon is a small, usually transparent image within a Web page. At the time Your computer downloads the image, the HTML code of that page is capable of passing along certain information. The second form of Web beacon is a short script of code that is loaded within your browser at the time Your computer plays a video. The browser runs this script, making it capable of passing along certain information. The types of information collected by a Web beacon may include the IP address of the computer retrieving the image or playing the video, the browser type used to retrieve the image or play the video, the time when the image or video was retrieved or played, and the values contained within previously set Cookies. If You disable Cookies in your browser, Web Beacons will be unable to track Your specific use of the Site, but some areas of the Site or Services may not work properly.

We may contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. For example, we may use the services of a marketing company to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our Site. To do this, we may use Cookies and Web beacons provided by our partners on this Site. We may also enable advertisers and ad servers to promote third-party products and/or services by placing advertisements on the Site. These advertisers and ad servers may use Cookies and/or Web beacons in order to monitor information related to advertisements. Advertisers we support in this way include AudienceScience, Inc. who collects information on behalf of P&G. The information collected helps our advertisers, our third party partners and us learn things like what kinds of customers our Site attracts, which of our advertisers' products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Please be aware that clicking on advertisements for third parties' products and services will direct You to the website of a third-party and/or the advertiser. This Privacy Policy does not cover the privacy practices of any advertisers or ad servers.

### Information From Other Sources

We may receive Personal Information about You from other sources like telephone, fax or email, from third-parties that provide services for us in connection with the Site or Services, as well as from other users and third parties to whom You have voluntarily provided information. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from You via the Site or Services. This Privacy Policy does not restrict our use of that additional information.

### Third-Party Websites

The Site or Services may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every website they visit. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Site or Services and does not apply to information collected by third parties through these third-party websites. The ability to access information of third-parties from the Site or Services, or links to other websites or locations, is for Your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such third-parties, their services, other websites, locations or their contents.

### How We Use Information Generally

We use Personal Information You submit to us to respond to requests that You make, to improve the Site or Services, to better tailor the features, performance and support of the Site or Services, and to offer You additional information, opportunities, and functionality. You are not required to provide Personal Information to access most features of the Site and Services, but we may from time to time offer optional or additional features, access to which may require You to register or provide Personal Information. In those instances, we will use Personal Information You submit to us to administer Your registration and access.

If You provide your email address to us, You consent to our contacting You using that email address, until such time as you expressly instruct us that You no longer with to receive such communications.

We may create Non-Personal Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as Your name or email address) that makes the information personally identifiable to You. We may use Non-Personal Information to analyze usage patterns so that we may enhance the Site or Services. We reserve the right to use and disclose Non-Personal Information to third-parties in our discretion.

Further, Grab Media may use or distribute aggregated data that does not personally identify You without restriction and is not required to seek additional permission from You regarding such internal or external use of such information.

If You provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not publicly associate such feedback with Your Personal Information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the Personal Information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Use Of Information For Behavioral Advertising

Grab Media uses information collected from end users of the Site, as well as information that we collect from end users of the numerous websites where we deliver videos, to develop profiles of end users for purposes of selecting the advertisements that we display, sometimes known as "behavioral advertising." Grab Media complies with the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising (the "Principles") published by the Digital Advertising Alliance. We may disclose information collected for purposes of behavioral advertising to advertisers (including AudienceScience who collects information on behalf of P&G), to the third parties who operate the websites through which we collected the information, or to other third parties in connection with behavioral advertising. By agreeing to this Privacy Policy, you are consenting to our collection, use and disclosure of information for behavioral advertising purposes. You may withdraw your consent or modify your preferences regarding our information collection and use of your information for such purposes by indicating your preferences at [http://www.aboutads.info/choices.](http://www.aboutads.info/choices)

### Disclosure Of Information

Access to most features of the Site is available without charge. From time to time we may offer optional or additional features that are subject to charges, or we may decide to cease providing free access to the Site or Services. If at any time we do collect payment information from You, like credit card numbers (collectively, "Payment Information"), we will not disclose that information to any third party except for purposes of processing payments for Services that you elect to purchase.

We may disclose Your Personal Information, including Payment Information:

(a) if such disclosure is made to comply with the law or an order issued by a court or an authorized administrative agency, respond to a subpoena, protect the rights or property of Grab Media or its affiliated companies, prevent a crime, or protect the personal safety or rights of others;

(b) to our service providers for the purpose of providing Services on our behalf, such as customer service, information technology services, and hosting services;

(c) as part of a merger or consolidation, or part of the sale of all or substantially all the stock or assets of the business to which the information pertains;

(d) as part of a disposition in a bankruptcy proceeding in a transaction approved by the bankruptcy court; and

(e) in other instances when we have gotten your express permission before disclosure.

Please be aware that when You voluntarily transmit or post Personal Information on public portions of the Site, that information will be displayed to anyone who has access to those postings or transmissions and can be collected and used by others. This may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. We cannot be responsible for Personal Information You voluntarily display, disclose or distribute on the Site.

You authorize Grab Media to share Personal Information with our affiliates (such as a parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control) and we will require our affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

In the event Grab Media goes through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, Your Personal Information will likely be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Grab Media or its assets may continue to use and disclose Your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose information for purposes in connection with behavioral advertising, as described above, provided that we comply with the Principles.

Just to be clear, if the law requires that we first obtain Your express permission to disclose certain particular categories of Personal Information, we will always be sure to obtain Your express permission before making such disclosures.

### How To Limit The Ability Of Others To See Your Information

You need to be careful when disclosing information about yourself because Your information that You provide may reveal Your identity. It is up to You to make sure You are comfortable with the information You choose to provide us. YOU DO NOT HAVE TO PROVIDE ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION OF ANY KIND TO US, BUT YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOU MAY NOT BE ABLE TO ACCESS SOME PORTION OF THE SITE OR USE SOME OF OUR SERVICES UNLESS YOU DO.

### Accessing And Controlling Your Information

If we possess any Personal Information about You, you may review and correct any inaccuracies in that Personal Information by contacting us by email at the address stated below. You authorize us to use and disclose any new or modified information that you provide in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please remember, however, if we have already disclosed some of Your Personal Information, we can not access that Personal Information any longer and cannot force the deletion or modification of that Personal Information by the parties to whom we have made those disclosures. YOU UNDERSTAND AND AGREE THAT WE ARE UNDER NO OBLIGATION TO DELETE PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU HAVE PREVIOUSLY CHOSEN TO PROVIDE US.

### Security

Grab Media is committed to protecting the security of Personal Information so that we can treat it consistent with this Privacy Policy. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures consistent with industry-standards to help protect Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, including physical, electronic, and administrative safeguards to protect data collected for purposes of behavioral advertising. Even though we have taken steps to ensure that Personal Information is not intercepted, accessed, used, or disclosed by unauthorized persons, You should know that we cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information. You assume all responsibility and risk for Your use of the Site and/or Services and the information You post or access through the Site and/or Services.

### Changes

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any substantial changes to it, we will notify you of any such changes by posting notice of the changes on the Site. Any such modifications become effective upon Your continued access to and/or use of the Site or Services five (5) days after we first post the changes on the Site or otherwise provide you with notice of such modifications. It is Your sole responsibility to check the Site from time to time to view any such changes to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If You do not agree to any changes, if and when such changes may be made to this Privacy Policy, You must cease access to the Site and use of the Services. If you have provided Your email address to us, You give us permission to email you for the purpose of notification as described in this paragraph.

### Contact

If You have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at: privacy@grab-media.com. Thank you for using our Site.
